My fellow Texans, have you heard all the laws that are going into place tomorrow?
September 1st?
You haven't?
Hold on.
Let me show you.
If you live in Texas, you need to watch this.
It is now a class B or C misdemeanor for failure to identify yourself if you're driving.
How do y'all feel about that?
And also look at the bottom.
Temporary license plates are illegal now in the state of Texas.
All of these new laws take effect September 1st.
Please, please identify yourself going forward.
Oh, there's more.
Hold on.
To be almost 800 laws that were passed during the Texas legislature season that are going to be going into effect.
Let's take a look at what some of them are.
Let's start with House Bill 900.
It brings a big change to school libraries, and it requires vendors to put a rating on all books.
Books that are deemed sexually explicit would be removed from bookshelves, and those deemed sexually relevant will require parents' permission.
House Bill 4520, which states that teachers are not allowed to distribute anything considered harmful material.
In doing so, they can receive the disqualification of their retirement benefits, and here it states exactly what those harmful materials are deemed, which, if you look at most of the books that are required reading for middle school and high school students, there are sexually relevant topics that could be considered harmful material.
So there will likely have to be a massive change when it comes to what required readings are for Texas students, likely putting Texas students behind most of their peers in other schools.
There's also the Crown Act, which is actually great to see.
It bans any race-based discrimination in education, among other areas, and in particular, Black women and Black men being allowed to wear their hair in their natural styles.
There are so many of these that are very important, and I likely won't be able to get through all of them, but I will show as many of them as possible and feel free to pause to read.
But chaplains in schools, Senate Bill 763 allows for unlicensed religious chaplains to counsel students in public schools.
As you can see right below that, there is an article that is linked that 100 Texas chaplains sign letter pushing school districts to say no to chaplains aiding in student mental health care.
If that's not a fucking red flag, I don't know what is.
House Bill 3 requires schools to have armed officers or armed staff members.
Can't lie, very worried about that.
I think this is a tactic that is going to lead to the unaliving of children in schools, if I'm being honest.
Senate Bill 17 bans diversity, equity, and inclusion in offices programs.
Senate Bill 1517 prohibits public schools and universities from implementing academic boycotts of foreign countries if it prevents students and faculty from conducting research or interacting with their scholars.
Senate Bill 14 bans transgender youth from accessing transitioning health care like puberty blockers and hormone therapy.
We are likely going to see a larger rise in kids with suicidal ideations and kids who actually do to end up taking their own lives.
Senate Bill 12, a direct attack on drag.
Senate Bill 15, a direct attack on trans women in sports.
Senate Bill 1933, which supposedly fixes irregularities, but is only applied to Harris County, which is the largest district in the state of Texas.
And to close it out, what she was saying is Senate Bill 1551, which requires you to identify yourself when you are in a traffic stop.
If not, you will be charged like they're they can file charges on you and arrest you for not identifying yourself.
So be be mindful, be cautious, be careful.
OK, if you have children in the education system that that is between K through 12, please go read up on these laws and know what's being taught to your children.
And if you are getting pulled over in the state of Texas as a tomorrow, pull out your ID, pull out your license, your registration, give them the information.
OK, do not do not fail to identify yourself if you are pulled over in a traffic stop, because a lot of people probably are unaware that this bill will go into effect tomorrow.
And yes, you can be charged for not identifying yourself.
So please, Texans, be careful, go educate yourselves on what has been happening in our Senate in the quiet of the night as they've been passing all this stuff.
So stay safe, people.
Stay safe.